Now I'll turn it over
to the reporters here
I'd like to ask
Actor Lee Hyesung
You're currently
in a golden age
since your debut
How did you two
first meet?
Please tell your story
Actor Lee Hyesung
["Love Mate"]
We met
at a shooting set
[Two months ago]
Hyesung
Check the C stand
in the greenroom
Yes, sir
Did I
meet him before?
Don't you remember
"My Crazy Family"?
He acted
Yoon Minhyung there
Wow, he's grown
by leaps and bounds
He used to be
a cutie little boy
Guess he's not acting
anymore now
That's why
he's working here
It's no use acting
for such a long time
He's still just
an unknown actor, huh?
It's pretty
Yeah, it is
Have I…
met you before?
Are you hitting
on me now?
What?
Wait a minute